[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly ____ hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often necessary to associate a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data point in ____ to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although the mountain was not steep, the raging river could not descend with sufficient rapidity to ____ its overflowing its banks.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has ____ published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The latter has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Teachers identified aspects ____ to the task of teaching, such as their interactions with students and their capacity to influence student achievement.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The goal of the Program is to ____ students to investigate significant problems in human physiology using modern technology.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Bali has failed to ____ a proposed ten year program to work on sustainable production and consumption.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Users want to maximize their access to ____ information, without losing sight of the amount of energy it takes them to get that information.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is unable to ____ that Iran is planning to build nuclear weapons.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I asked for a concise ____ of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right ____ of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An error will ____ if this software is not installed on the user's machine.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She claimed that the disproportionate number of non-native speakers in the survey did not ____ the results.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Iraq has entered into a critical ____ where there is a great danger of civil war.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A new class of antibiotic drugs is not expected to ____ in the immediate future.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ your books and check each other's writing.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most ____ function of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This political biography has fully succeeded in its ____ of restoring Shevardnadze's place in history.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people buy supplementary vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their ____ food.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The New Investigator Competition is an award for the best paper by a graduate student, carrying with it a prize valued at ____ \ufffd\ufffd500.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be brief and to ____ all that is important.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ultimate ____ in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was not until about 500 years ago that scientists and doctors began to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ people without jobs to business that are looking for workers.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Luckily, ____ to total coincidence, the men's and women's basketball teams started most of their games on the road.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Engineers were deeply concerned about the O-ring design on the booster rocket before the launch, but were unable to ____ managers at NASA of the importance of that problem.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On hearing of the terrorist ____ the president called an immediate meeting of his top advisers.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This principle can be applied to ____ educational and medical issues.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is the first step to permanently limiting enrollment growth, something that seemed only a ____ possibility earlier this year.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to intervene in the ____ over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The final topic presents the impact of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their ____ on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the ____ arts.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that genetically modified food can ____ people's health.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will ____ in a series of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not confront any tester who is cheating, but will ____ the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has little chance of success in its ____ to reduce crime unless it creates more jobs.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't ____ their most serious health risk.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the ____ words used and the explicit claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will ____ attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I think Kerry's biggest error, as a politician, is that he failed to ____ himself from Bush in any meaningful way.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The airport police always ____ the need for everyone to be vigilant with their suitcases and other bags.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new government proposals also ____ that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The paper was unable to attract sufficient ____ and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some types of ____ are dirty, dangerous or not well-paid. It is often poor immigrants to a country who take such jobs.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The doctor's claim was ____ hypocrisy. He more interested in making money than his patient's health.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While its lack of clarity was seen by some early critics as a clear ____ of error and confusion, it was seen by others as a hallmark of genius.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The scientists that constitute the committee all work in the ____ of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You should ____ a little more in class discussions. This will help to improve your spoken English.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his ____ to correctly inform the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students worked in groups to ____ (or dis____) a series of mathematical statements.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government blamed its defeat in the elections on failure to ____ its policies clearly enough.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that there is an abundant ____ of oil waiting to be discovered at the bottom of deep oceans.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government will never ____ drug-taking, but it should do more to reduce the number of school-age drug users.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Upon completion of your program requirements, you will need to apply for a ____ to teach in the state of Ohio.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher should ____ presentation styles and take into account diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is often necessary to ____ a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is unclear whether this facility will be able to ____ complete missiles or only some major component.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She claimed that the disproportionate number of non-native speakers in the survey did not ____ the results.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to organize his ____ to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her chances of success in the examinations will continue to ____ unless she starts working harder very soon.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This ____ can be applied to various educational and medical issues.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key role the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult ____ from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will notice an ____ that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police have not been able to ____ a motive for the brutal killing.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Kennan had no ____ that the Soviets had regional, if not global, ambitions.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is more than one successful ____ to teach and learn a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts measure this ____ according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has set itself the ____ of reducing teenage pregnancy by 20% in the next 10 years.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no shame in ____ if you have tried your best.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I understand her ____ to speak English in class. She has only just arrived at the school.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as ____ and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since Ramadan emphasizes community aspects and since everyone eats dinner at the same time, Muslims often invite one another to ____ in the Ramadan evening.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ to be recognized, to be considered important is not superficial. It is a basic human drive.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to ____ yourself and your property are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I would set my classes up for failure if I did not ____ this very clear, but often overlooked, fact.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ fits well with the fact that his mental health did not deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To remain eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory progress toward a ____ according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd ____ a zero point test with questions from the year before in random order with random answers.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government should pay particular attention to reducing unemployment ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The essay asks students to complete several tasks, giving the students ____ examples of human rights cases.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most countries have a ____ by which parents can decide if a film is suitable for their children.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The board was unable to ____ a candidate in the first round because of disagreement over candidates' performance.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In some businesses it is the ____ that the eldest son takes over when the father dies.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ the money they donate to poor countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Before economists implement ____ measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After Iraq some people feel strongly that the USA should never again ____ in the affairs of other countries.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the sports of mountain-climbing and table tennis. In the first you can get killed; in the second usually not.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We hoped to find ____ data on why certain people donate time and money and others don't.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some solutions exist to ____ the performance of these devices, but naturally there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The population of a country will ____ if more people die than are born.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The main ____ of a teacher is to teach.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To ____ sales success always imply, in every possible way, that the person you're dealing with is smarter, better-looking, slimmer, and more successful than they really are.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this field of study will have ____ opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "European governments strongly condemn the kidnapping of a German ____ worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will need to get your parents' assent for your attendance at the sex ____ classes.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we do not start to consume less oil, there is ____ to be none left by the end of the century.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to specify in sufficient detail the definition of a medication ____ used in the study.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation ____ that is used in virtually all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My ____ mathematics teacher is sick so we have had a substitute for the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The headmaster's decision is sure to ____ much discussion among teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Immigrants ____ more than 20% of the total population.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In general, when you paraphrase, you use about the same number of words to ____ the idea that the writer uses in the text.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In history lessons we learn about many ____ peoples such as the Egyptians who built the pyramids, and Roman emperors like Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies demonstrate that the state was not able to ____ discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a ____ effect on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We have not yet been able to find out the ____ reason why he attacked the teacher.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, despite the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government reports a ____ decrease in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company report did not do much to ____ the reasons for the fall in business in the previous year.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This will be a reading lesson. Please do not ____ it by trying to talk.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Distance learning is the most ____ phenomenon occurring in higher education today.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In most countries of the world you need to get a ____ before you can drive a car.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Next, we examine eight aspects of the paradigm ____ in second language teaching.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Media center users must ____ to the same standards of behavior expected of other library visitors.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students ____ careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These results ____ that substantial numbers of students attending the school are not attaining minimum levels of literacy and mathematical competency.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the ____ in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Prime Minister broke off her visit to China ____ to an urgent problem at home.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But it is not a substitute for ____ food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government does not plan to admit any more immigrants unless they can ____ that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Scientists are working on a robot that can ____ to the deepest parts of the Pacific Ocean.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Regional Oral History Office has moved to a ____ location.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Because of the interactive nature of the classroom, absences will significantly affect your ____ in the course.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I am no ____ in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have had ____ chances to improve your behaviour. Now it's too late.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Don't ____ me in your plan - I want nothing to do with it.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to ____ or address the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most economists believe that oil is the most important ____ in today's world.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All children below the age of 16 have the obligation to ____ school.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has failed in its primary task, namely to ____ unemployment.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you change your address or place of study, please ____ your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A records check was unable to ____ his claim that he possessed a valid license.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The assessment was not ____ of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola prior to its release.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most countries have a code by which parents can decide if a film is ____ for their children.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The head teacher decided to push through her idea though most of the teachers were ____ it.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a ____ symbol of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a constant ____ at all heights.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a ____ solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is set to reject the parents' request to ____ their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We can separate white light into its component colors with a prism and use an ____ prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a remote corner of Antarctica can ____ an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you don't start working harder, we will ____ your right to leave the school at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some students will ____ that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little effect on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will ____ the carpet if you come inside with those dirty shoes.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An orange pencil is not a suitable ____ to do your homework with.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One fortunate ____ of rainy weather is that the dust is regularly washed off, reducing problems with the machinery.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since the discovery of cave paintings, we can ____ what animals looked like thousands of years ago.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is no coincidence that the early proponents of so-called public ____ were socialists.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are reliable and flexible, enjoy solving tasks independently and are committed to achieving ____ performance, then this is the job for you.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ new students otherwise one or two teachers will have to lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It took the Brazilian football player a little while to ____ to the speed and hardness of the English football league.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a genuine example of how the right ____ and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was a ____ thinker and an artist, albeit a rather unsuccessful one.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not acknowledge the ____ developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What the headlines failed to ____ was that democratic parties captured more than 60 percent of the ballots cast.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the excitement of bringing the Internet into our classrooms, we sometimes forget to ____ our learners appropriately.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "One ____ reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in labour productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In sports events it is a good idea at the start of the game to ____ energy that you are going to need later.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He will never be a good teacher. He has no ____ of the class.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These poems ____ a good grade, but because you gave them in late I have to give you a 0.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many students doing an important test try to ____ their answers with their hand or a book. They don't want their neighbour seeing what they have written.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you do not have a particular title in mind, but wish to suggest that the library ____ more material on a specific subject, please enter your name.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The private ____ offers many opportunities for students with a history or liberal arts background.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He reported that the presidential search committee has been formed and thanked some groups for forwarding ____ nominees.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school's ____ have been improved recently with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is the completely rational ____ of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Your low grades will ____ you of the chance of taking part in sports trips.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the operation may just ____ the problems.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government tried hard to ____ its decision, but most people believe it was a serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is ____ for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The one ____ in the classroom that belongs to me is the old typewriter.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The rat lungworm, is the ____ cause of eosinophilic meningitis worldwide.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was not the tradition of going to school; it was expected that you'd go to work and ____ to the family.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ of all students in grade 12 shows that more than 70% think they are given too much homework.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I think your ____ is wrong. You should be in science class now, not ESL.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking harsh actions ____ communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My father is going to ____ to Germany at the end of 2004.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The employees are ____ opposed to the management's plans to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Can you please explain the ____ by which students are placed in ESL class?", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I'm not sure that his parents realize the ____ of the problems he is having in school.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She discussed the schedule for implementing the system through April 2003 and outlined ____ potential advantages of the system.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to ____ prejudice.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Users are guided through a complete ____ of statistical computing: preparing data, performing analysis, viewing output.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Customers found no benefit in ____ -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you choose not to ____ or to withdraw from the study at any time, there will be no penalty.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The self-hatred that this ____ inflicted led the children to attempt to wash their skin white with scouring powder.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an image war, trying to ____ the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the administration still did not have time to ____ all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Neither of the two strategies was ____ in terms of performance.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is the single most important deed a district ____ can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers ____ that the problems in the Middle East may strain the relationship between some of the Arab and Israeli students at the school.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What motives have thus incited him to ____ all the hardships and temptations he encountered on his way from a miserable life to an honorable one.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This ____ is simple but has a significant drawback.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a ____ sheet, write a thorough statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The main ____ of living in the city is that you are close to good shopping and entertainment. Of course, city life has many dis____s too.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It seems natural that we would want to employ nurses from overseas; after all we ____ everything else.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A sound card is an essential ____ of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to ____ the issue of global warming. They claim it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will collapse and whether the United States should ____ its collapse has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Her perspective was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. ____ is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has failed in its primary task, ____ to reduce unemployment.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a ____ corner of Antarctica can disrupt an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A half century ago the ____ over state regulation of railroads was the chief issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Scientists are hoping that it may soon be possible to ____ the weather.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the individual knows in advance when he or she wishes to ____ for time away from the workplace, the individual should complete the preliminary request form.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You should use the bathroom ____ to coming to class.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the master plan to ____ whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of ____ choices that a criminal would make in the decision to commit a crime.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The fact that speech is likely to result in some violence or in destruction of ____ is not enough to justify its suppression.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To test for a ____ sentence, see if it can stand alone and still mean something.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The result will be an immediate and ____ increase in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He found a serious error in the work and did a very careful study to ____ the correct results.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She had no ____ to practice architecture in the District.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an ____ tool for university life and work, and a valuable privilege.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Online students need a ____ of realistically assessing their readiness for the demands of taking a course in the online environment.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Police are continuing to ____ the two men who were seen behaving suspiciously just before the bomb exploded.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Caesar showed no ____ to accept the office of \"dictator for life\" in February 44 B.C.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will ____ attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A significant ____ of the continent is characterized by water scarcity.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must ____ it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is impossible to ____ a good grade in this course without reading the material.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What we are really discussing is whether the industrialized countries can ____ the pensions promised by their respective governments.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very ____ email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the ____ may just magnify the problems.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the opinion of the Committee, was not a ____ witness.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not ____ a valid parking permit will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not difficult to speculate on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our ____ to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She expects to complete her education and ____ her doctorate between 2012 and 2015, after which she intends to become a mathematics professor.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ that led to the train crash are being investigated by the police.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We have found that students are more likely to complete a community health project if they ____ a team.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war ____ Iraq is an appropriate occasion to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While I don't ____ this as absolutely the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It seems that the mind cannot ____ the necessary information from what is supplied to it.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Check with your academic advisor if you are uncertain whether this will count as a ____ towards your graduation.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Try to communicate that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an ____ solution.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The result will be an immediate and ____ increase in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dr. Blumenthal begins by analyzing why health care reform ____ failed to pass Congress in 1994.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One crucial reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in ____ productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the attempt was an ____ failure.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot ____ it.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This international degree course has been ____ created for international students in their final stage of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "English may be a global language but it is not yet a proper ____ for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most significant risk factor in predicting whether a person will ____ a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you have the amnio test late in pregnancy and are carrying a baby with Downs Syndrome, it will be too late to ____ the pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government raised taxes, deciding to ____ the loud protests in the media.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We wanted to ____ a long-term relationship that could grow with our company.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you change your address or place of study, please ____ your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The prompt response of the Hu Jintao government has won ____ praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a ____ consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher's threat to give the student a detention had an immediate ____ on his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Facts surrounding the diagnosis of the child's condition are in ____ dispute.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her problems are close to the surface and ____ to be expressed in more direct, less symbolic, behavioral and emotional terms.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What is your ____ of his recent odd behaviour?", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people advocate government elections every four years ____ of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The evidence is overwhelming that prediction markets provide a more ____ prediction than polls.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ its main attention to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the standard ____ for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite ____ today but was not apparent before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They are currently involved in a battle ____ Occidental Petroleum to save their land and their way of life.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There were many ____ but complex reasons why he gave up his well-paid job.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The business manager could not explain the ____ in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no ____ having a law if the police are not willing to enforce it.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Before making our ____ we need to consider the issue of financial support.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What would you ____ to do today? Write a dictation or watch a video?", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One of the great problems in social dynamics is that the dynamic systems are not ____ and are frequently subject to unpredictable change.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most serious ____ raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents communicate by email, but they cannot ____ on it.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Engineers were deeply concerned about the O-ring design on the booster rocket before the launch, but were unable to ____ managers at NASA of the importance of that problem.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The fact that he can only speak a little English is sure to ____ his already severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Later in the year they plan to ____ up to 4000,00 more solar panels in a student village to be built for the university.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Teachers must ____ students and supervise activities in the computer room.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He is learning that treatments that worked fine in cities don't always ____ well here, where patients may drive several hours to obtain medical care.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have made excellent ____ in English this year. You will soon no longer need to take ESL lessons.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the ____ of the Committee, was not a credible witness.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "So when Solomon died (sometime around 920 BC) he left a vacuum of power which his weak son Rehoboam was not ____ of filling.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The director planned to ____ the information to the workforce at the next general assembly.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an ____ pattern that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you cannot ____ such a statement, you must verify that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to assist you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and therefore decided to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government report is set to ____ its report on nuclear energy tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There has been no ____ statement about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many birds ____ south in the winter to find warmer temperatures.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Your composition must ____ an introduction, a conclusion and three body paragraphs.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government must not ____ in taking harsh actions against communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The lecture is the most ____ teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Roman Jewish population did not ____ during Sixtus' reign; indeed, there was always movement of Jews in and out of the region.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Administrators and supervisors are expected to see that those who report to them are informed about, understand and ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ learning vocabulary as the single most important thing that ESL students should do.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you want to know whether an ____ is common or not, look it up in Google.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I ____ the cafeteria at lunchtime. It's too crowded and noisy.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is unclear whether this facility will be able to ____ complete missiles or only some major component.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a rational ____ but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Governments cannot govern without the broad ____ of the people.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most countries that went to war in Iraq now ____ their decision.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people ____ the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to gain control of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for ____ attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to ____ prejudice.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The study also found that both genders get a similar benefit from the therapy, which reduced mortality ____ in women by an estimated 43%.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are being quizzed on how well you understand the information in your required readings, so ____ your answers on what is written in the Hunt textbook.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The wishes of parents must not always ____ the recommendations of the teachers about the course choices of the child.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From my ____ as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are due to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Contact between infected and uninfected people can ____ disease.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On the rare occasion when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than ____ hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thorough cleaning must always ____ chemical disinfection of any equipment.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must ____ a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this field of study will have ____ opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The prime minister has decided to cancel the planned visit to Batavia in ____ of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an ____ against bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You must ____ copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should highlight the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Asia is our closest ____ and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and exchange culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most students are neutral about the suggestion to ____ the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will need to form project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your ____ to organize meetings.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ factor in our decision is how long it will take.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Another ____ meaning of due is the date on something has to be done, as in Don't forget. Your project is due tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The \"Maximize\" position says that we should give priority to whatever ____ produces the greatest net health benefit.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unfortunately, hunger is no ____ problem in the United States, where the disparity between the affluent and the indigent is considerable.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a general rule, all persons wishing to ____ the conference must register and pay for participation.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The best ____ is to change the nutrient solution every week instead of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A wife's going out to work is not deemed a violation of her marital obligations if her working is not ____ to her family's interests.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to ____ problem-solving strategies that offer clear practical solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Teachers can ____ that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The final ____ of the day was an optional tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to settle the dispute by the efforts of the ____ community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A small proportion of the government were ____ the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The wishes of parents must not always ____ the recommendations of the teachers about the course choices of the child.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "That was not a very ____ thing to do.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The medical company decided to ____ production of its heart drug when it heard reports of the unexplained deaths of many people who had been taking it.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dmitrieva and Kuptsova adopt an ____ approach and understand culture as a realm of signs and meanings.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will be required to know the questions and issues that the various authors raise and the approaches they ____ in their research.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The minister was unwilling to ____ on the changes in the price of oil in the next few months.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's ____ is that they will increase exports by 20% next year.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to design and deliver a ____ course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For some years in the UK personal computers have been used to provide sensory stimulation in schools for children with ____ and multiple learning difficulties.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have had no chance to ____ changes of this sort systematically, but simply offer them as examples of processes that we expect to be completed.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't ____ their most serious health risk.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The tree responds this way because the tree needs to ____ food again before it starves.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The essay asks students to complete several tasks, giving the students ____ examples of human rights cases.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not invest the ____ of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are one or two ____ spelling problems but in general this is an excellent piece of writing.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We wanted to ____ that the resonators worked, and our major theoretical assumptions were correct.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many students doing an important test try to ____ their answers with their hand or a book. They don't want their neighbour seeing what they have written.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As one of its many uses to ____ learning, the Internet is increasingly being used as a forum for students to give feedback to each other.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not related to university business must be limited and must not ____ in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was ____ that he did not do well in the vocabulary test. I know he had learned most of the words.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has set up a ____ to inquire why more young people have started smoking in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but ____ an opportunity explore topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the new hotel has been well-chosen: halfway between the airport and the beach.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ the reasons for your lack of success.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The principal problem facing the world this century is how to reduce ____ warming.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an attempt to ____ their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Class data will be collected to compare perceived overweight and attempt at dieting with ____ weight risk classification.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is difficult to change an unhealthy eating ____ that has developed from a very early age.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The patient was not at all happy with the ____ of treatment she received while in hospital.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university follows a ____ policy of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This may ____ relationships between children and parents, and necessitate the involvement of child welfare services.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing ____ is a distinct problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is the completely ____ response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I appreciate the reasons for your failure to hand in the work on time. Nevertheless, our ____ requires me to give you a zero.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we are to ____ in creating a true sense of citizenship in our students, we won't do so by offering an all-purpose, first-year global civics course.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government wants to make it ____ for the police to keep suspected terrorists in prison for 90 days before bringing them to trial.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This semester-long project begins with an overview in which students think about how to ask scientific questions and ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When Penn State decided not to cancel classes, it seemed like a safe and ____ decision.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The head teacher is thinking of introducing a school uniform. Most students are ____ the idea.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Before economists ____ drastic measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Car companies spend a ____ sum of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The naval and air forces failed to ____ their schedules and the carrier planes arrived a half hour later than expected.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because of the shortage of wheat, ____ to persistent wet weather, the price of bread has risen in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic growth was rapid and its benefits were widely ____ throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its modern languages department to meet the growing interest.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to protest about the government's decision to ____ the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Once you've chosen the course or courses you wish to take, you should ____ COM so that we can reserve a place for you.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After an ____ period of introduction and practice, the German course begins with Chapter 1 in the text Deutsch: Na klar!", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Working with the Teacher Assistant is not ____ but recommended.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In Iraq the whole ____ of government was destroyed and had to be rebuilt.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Board may ____ that those actions created a hostile or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school made a mistake when buying new computers. They are not ____ with the printers we have.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Ruhrgebiet is a large urban ____ in north west Germany.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not ____ unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not steady with time; a fact which could ____ be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is will continue to ____ problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the words 'uninterested ' and 'disinterested'.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people allege that the reasons for invading Iraq were to ____ control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no ____ of an original idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a ____ solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "China has experienced dynamic ____ in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your composition must ____ an introduction, a conclusion and three body paragraphs.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thus, the results obtained are consistent with the popular ____ that alcohol intoxication causes males to view women as more attractive.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thus, there is no question but that the donor intends this gift to be for the ____ use of Princeton University.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The thesis is unoriginal and lacks ____ into the key issues.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students must have ____ to a PC that has at least a 700 MHz processor.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The name of this website is 'A ____ to learning English.'", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is an opportunity to ____ a more demanding curriculum while having an equal opportunity to share in the full benefits of university life.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their background and ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people do not ____ a top engineering education with a liberal arts setting.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We will not prevail unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are ____ to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When the moisture con____s, heat is released into the air, making it warmer and less ____ than its surroundings.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When the USA expelled two Russian diplomats, the Russian ____ was to do the same.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our ____ feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Conversely, rising wage rates often ____ workers to try to work fewer hours as they become rich enough to afford more leisure.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His advice was to ____ short-term temptation when investing in stocks.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In most of Africa, for example, weaker institutions have failed to ____ restrictions on rulers and undemocratic power politics has been employed.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study programme in the Netherlands, you may be eligible for a ____ for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I have a ____ idea why she has been absent, but I'm not sure.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The women did not ____ emotionally to the comedy, but the men did, Filipowicz concludes.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last ____ of the twentieth century started in 1990 and ended on 31 December 1999.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Despite the overall satisfaction that the program was ____ successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ more rapidly if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher decided to ____ the activity when it became clear that the students didn't understand what to do.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will present the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is ____ the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages ____ from a moderate amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ that at least 80% of the students will pass with the top grade.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not really her ____ that she comes late to school so often. She lives a long way away, and often gets stuck in a traffic jam.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Iraq is ____ in a state of civil war.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Obviously the result of many years of reading and reflection, this ____ study contains detailed summaries of dozens of works, both major and minor.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She needed to earn enough money to be able to ____ London's sky-high prices.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was not the ____ of this book to discuss whether America can win the war, or whether it must lose it.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Researchers at the university plan to ____ a survey into what makes people over-drink.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The first effort to produce a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to ____ in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is set to ____ the parents' request to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's ____ is that the bomb was set off by a recent immigrant.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You ____ us all an apology for using this forum for your personal beliefs when it is a forum for scientific reasoning.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Dr. Blumenthal begins by analyzing why health care reform ____ failed to pass Congress in 1994.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We hoped to find relevant data on why ____ people donate time and money and others don't.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is NOT a ____ statistic and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The latest employment figures contradict the government's recent ____ that more people now have jobs than for many years.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best ____ of your essay is the fact that it was very easy to follow your line of argument.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her sadness when she only came third in the music competition.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company's ____ is that they will increase exports by 20% next year.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Mississippi is a ____ river.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is especially important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not competent to ____ their children.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ the cafeteria at lunchtime. It's too crowded and noisy.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "\"I'll ____ you these 7 Pokemon cards for your 8 Yugioh cards.\"", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was found that only 10 of these comparisons were acceptably consistent, meaning that their inconsistency ____ exceeded 35%.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the ____ was an utter failure.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the ____ of the brain.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the US government knew in advance about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How can you tell if the book, article, website, or other ____ you located is a valid, credible source?", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is set to ____ the parents' request to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These documents have an ____ stamp, but I'm not convinced they are authentic.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some doctors have the ____ to use language that their patients do not understand.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can indirectly influence the ____ at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Cole Conservatory evolves from a Music Department with a long ____ of exceptional training for students from all backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government can ____ its message about the dangers of drinking if it increases the price of alcohol.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to ____ their spoken words describing an abstract concept or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The parent appears to have a ____ lack of understanding of child development, resulting in unrealistic expectations for child that may be harmful.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her problems began to ____ themselves after she was absent for more than a month.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Almost all of the world's countries ____ to the United Nations organization.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was a great ____ that the disease would spread to other farms. Hence all the sick cows had to be killed.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your answer should include three ____ causes of the disaster.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to release hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two companies have settled their ____ over patent issues and dropped legal actions.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We will ____ from this schedule throughout the semester, but the hand-out gives a good impression of our general focus.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To ____ their high salary, top managers like to refer to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We should not ____ the possibility that house prices will begin to fall.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Board provided an inadequate ____ of reasons for its 1981 decision.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a unique search ____ has paid off.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of scarce resources ____ competing ends.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He ____ failed to mention the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She will harm her chances of graduating unless she starts to ____ school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a cause of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can ____ the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Could you please ____ this book to its proper place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We need to ____ a test to measure the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has set up a programme to ____ refugees on entry to the country.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the past 30 years, the ____ in Africa has continued to deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special ____ will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people ____ before eating raw fish for the first time. They are not sure what it will taste like.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we ____ that the dimension of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a new computer for each of its teachers.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The book had arrived in stores by Sunday evening but store managers were under ____ instructions not to even open the boxes and put it on the shelves.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on individual drugs but they do not know so much how drugs ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to keep its promises and ____ was voted out of power at the next election.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Bright flashing lights ____ headaches in some people.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students choosing this option must ____ a faculty adviser from the departmental faculty who will supervise the student's program.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to be successful in business, it is certainly an ____ to be able to speak more than one language.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to organize his ____ to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the ____ without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He failed to ____ proof that he had completed an approved substance- abuse program as required.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Transportation is not an important ____ in the marketing cost of the new product.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Exam question: Distinguish between the ____ of the iris and the ____ of the cornea.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to exploit the resources that will allow them to ____ the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is heading into difficult ____ with its plans to ban smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For financial reasons the government had to cut the programme to help prisoners on their ____ from jail.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are six categories to ____ from, each containing five answers in ascending order of difficulty.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of ____ work, but it must comprise achievement that is over and above regular ____ activities.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was in 1827, near the beginning of his time ____ from the Allan family, that Poe witnessed his first collection of poetry.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people have to ____ their houses when war breaks out in their country.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since the U.S. flu vaccine ____ was cut in half early this month, shots are scarce, lines long and some people are certain to miss out.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a ____ policy that can respond and adapt to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people like to get up late and go to work late. Others ____ to be at work early so they have a long evening to enjoy.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ensure that the way we talk must not ____ any religious, ethnic, cultural, or political group.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is ____ that the summer rate cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We need to ____ entry to the cafeteria so that not all students are trying to buy a meal at the same time.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a ____ way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is unlikely to rise above the ____ of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The bottom of the Pacific Ocean is the most ____ region on Earth.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why do people still ____ in living near volcanoes?", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I think we should ____ her work more closely for the next few weeks. She needs to know that we are concerned about her progress.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Based on his research, Healey developed a system that combined the display of multiple values into a single ____ element.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A supervisor must not ignore, delay, or inappropriately ____ an student's request for assistance.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of the Olympic Games is five overlapping rings.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not ____ that he could have gained such a good grade without help from someone else.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Today women and men have the same ____ in western society. This wasn't always the case.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Corms have shapes ____ to bulbs, but do not contain fleshy scales.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ collection is complete and available for online access.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I think her problems in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's no use trying to ____ me that your father speaks 10 languages. I just don't believe you.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people think that the USA invaded Iraq because of oil. The ____ is much more complicated than that.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round cycle of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the background before you ____ the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How to increase employment and ____ crime are the two most serious problems that confront the new government.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A great ____ of discussion focused on observations which could solve the mystery by testing the predictions of the various hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a ____ implication on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "People today have become more conscious of their individual responsibility to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to compile a full application including: ____ sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the ____ can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We ____ all our efforts and resources to the education and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is ____ not a rational decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Each programme is designed to give students the opportunity to explore significant social, ____ and environmental issues using an innovative comparative model.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He certainly could not ____ the existence of major problems.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher look like she was going to ____ angrily when I came late, but fortunately for me, she didn't!", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is especially important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not ____ to supervise their children.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not ____ much space.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In order to make student learning ____ to real life experiences, learning environments must be authentic.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Occasional personal use of university computing resources for other purposes is permitted when it does not consume a ____ amount of those resources.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our very privilege makes us ____ of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to ____ career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Less educated minority parents are more likely to manifest a ____ of involvement in their child's schooling.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The cost of gas (petrol) will continue to ____ as the price of oil goes up or down.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is an American ____ which obviously puts him in a different category from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although nuclear power does not pollute the air, many people are against it because they fear an accident or terrorist ____ on a nuclear power station.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The priests of this ____ did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the interpretation of dreams", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Financial ____ is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What is your ____ criterion for a happy life? - Good health!", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although the mountain was not steep, the raging river could not ____ with sufficient rapidity to prevent its overflowing its banks.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not sum to 100% because many students were ____ on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to ____ this issue.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He is learning that treatments that worked fine in cities don't always fare well here, where patients may drive several hours to ____ medical care.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to ____ an extension with the TA regarding such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global society will ____ as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ \ufffd\ufffd10,000 to buy new computers next year for the science lab.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law ____ to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This interesting ____ offers the student of neuroscience access to an immense amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't ____ with police orders to disperse from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The latest ____ among the girls in the school is to wear different colour socks.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The court decided to ignore the opinion of the ____ health specialist.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a common belief that the universe is infinite. But who knows? Maybe one day we will ____ it has an edge or end.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the ____ still did not have time to cover all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Newton's Laws provide a good ____ of the flight of a baseball.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is extremely important to ____ the installation with all parties involved.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people have to ____ their houses when war breaks out in their country.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I ____ that we consider our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The US government plan to develop weapons that can be used from space. Many scientists, however, ____ the proposals as unworkable.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Who was the first person to ____ America? Most people say it was Columbus.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A sound card is an ____ component of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The agent's ____ for selling a house is usually a percentage of the sale price.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a logical ____ of having free will.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school has made the difficult decision to ____ the wearing of religious symbols in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At first there was a little ____ between the Japanese and Korean students, but this soon passed.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The sea froze over in the ____ cold.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ordinary people who are caught up in ____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Over the past 30 years, the ____ in Africa has continued to deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The high price of oil will ____ much of the company's profits this year.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Be certain to answer the question in its entirety. Be certain to ____ how and why you came to a particular conclusion.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During its congress, Committee failed to ____ even one woman to a leading position.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She will need an ____ performance to have any chance of winning the game. Her opponent is much better.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the school day until 4:30.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school has decided from now on to ____ its Teacher-Parent newsletter on the website, and not on paper.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The global trade agreements have failed to include meaningful, enforceable ____ or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is the first step to permanently limiting enrollment growth, something that seemed only a ____ possibility earlier this year.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since it was founded in 1999, the partnership program has been a key ____ in the dramatic increase in applications to the College.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The one ____ in the classroom that belongs to me is the old typewriter.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The contributors assert that teaching is a gendered occupation with low ____ and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to ____ information about patterns of ties among social actors.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In 2000, over seventy percent of India's population, and ____ three quarters of its poor, lived in rural areas.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do not commit the ____ error of believing you can pass the course without doing the coursework.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The main function of the ____ is to recommend a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government ____ a warning about the dangers of terrorist attack in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company directors are confident that business will ____ in the new year.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy ____ to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In infants without a family history of food allergies, there is no need to ____ or avoid any specific foods.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to remove the ____ that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer ____ or modify grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Let me ____ again that you must work alone; you are not permitted to get help from anyone else.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We should avoid the ____ of assuming that we will ever be able to comprehend the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The death of Princess Diana was an ____ that shocked the whole world.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We did not base our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or ____ of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Be sure to ____ and disinfect feeding equipment and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a result of the ____ amount of evidence for evolution accumulated over the last two centuries, we can safely conclude that evolution has occurred.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Blair will need to persuade the Americans that Europeans will no longer ____ Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we ____ your request to amend the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We held that the entry was illegal because police failed to ____ their purpose before using the crowbar to pry the door open.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To ____ the project, a special event will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The first and only reliable line of defense ____ the acquisition or use of \"suitcase nuclear weapons\" by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main ____ of the proposed research is to investigate the influence of West African languages.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Hershey Corporation, however, already had a deal to ____ chocolate for the troops.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has succeeded in reducing unemployment ____ older people; conversely, young people are having ever more difficulty finding a job.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and ____ of cities and ways planners solve urban problems.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; thus it has had little opportunity to develop ____ disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The medical company decided to ____ production of its heart drug when it heard reports of the unexplained deaths of many people who had been taking it.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company report did not do much to ____ the reasons for the fall in business in the previous year.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people look back on their years at university as the happiest ____ in their lives.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government plans to introduce an ____ for long-term unemployed people to start looking for work again.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Our ____ surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The final topic presents the ____ of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "About a quarter of the ____ and secondary students typically did not interact with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable statistic and you should simply ____ it.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Did anyone ____ to solve question 11?", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the ____ to the general public in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I hesitate to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to ____ the lectures.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this ____ has covered a number of discrete issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ was determined by querying the number of research proposals received by RSPP and the direct costs associated with reviewing each proposal.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dr. Potts announced that he planned to ____ a broadly based committee of representatives to study the Indian issue.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although the agreement was ____ rather than voluntary, it led to substantial military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Tobacco smoke was a ____ of life up through the 1970s.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar symbol of ____ to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In many families precious objects like jewelry or photographs are handed down from one ____ to the next.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would resist and ____ that heritage.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Educational websites have the ____ suffix: .edu. For example, the URL of this website is: esl.fis.edu.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is a ____ chance to visit South Africa, and at the same time help build a school in the desert.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people say that he does not ____ the qualities to become president of this country.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The goal of the Program is to train students to ____ significant problems in human physiology using modern technology.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her work has continued to ____ since the divorce of her parents.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A very ____ response in real time is needed to record the optical emission while the gamma-ray burst is in progress.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to ____ the spread of crime?", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete against the firms from not ____ India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government will monitor the ____ in Iraq very carefully, but has not yet made any changes in its policy.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ every significant detail about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ your answer to a maximum of 100 words.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The merger of two sellers of that product in the area could not ____ market power significantly.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the ____ operating system will be more secure than ever before.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ come to school by bus, but my father is driving me this week.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on ____ matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of ____ grammar rules does always not correlate with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The proposed changes to the new law will ____ it of all its power.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your work will be penalized if you do not ____ it by the assigned deadline.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many arguments would not develop if people would ____ the words they use.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Board provided an inadequate ____ of reasons for its 1981 decision.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ was unclear. It had been hand-drawn and then copied using weak ink.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a stable domestic ____ would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If there is any question whether the individual might have a physical problem, the mental health professional should ____ a complete examination.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now dispute the ____ for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A ____ science experiment for young people is to investigate the growth of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The professor meets with each student for a half-hour private tutorial ____ three times during the semester.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the ____ of an actual disaster a new virtual bulletin board will help the campus take roll.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Alumni have expressed much positive reaction to the Alumni Association's recent initiatives to ____ its use of electronic newsletters and its Web site.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many shops these days have ____ doors. They open as soon as you approach.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He certainly could not deny the existence of ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police did not have the necessary ____ to cut the man free from the crashed car.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We must reverse the ____ of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not in the best interests of children if their parents are ____ protective of them.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Homes were built and sold to families in need at no ____ and no interest.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This ____ does not imply that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We can ____ that China is unlikely to put significant pressure on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such pressure.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic ____ is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Photographs ____ if they are left out in bright sunlight.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is usually easy for teachers to ____ if an ESL student has copied text from a webpage.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some farmers, especially those producing corn, hope that biofuels have a bright future, both as a new ____ of cheap energy and as a new ____ of revenue.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ to a new school in a new country is a difficult one for most students.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Law School will not permit you to take a ____ pass/fail unless you have received written permission.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate ____ of the witnesses, the police were able to identify the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Even the older generation does have some ____ of the Indonesian language.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a ____ of Indiana since at least December 31 of the previous year.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Research has indicated that the majority of teachers failed to ____ computers in direct classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The pass / ____ grade is not arbitrary. It was set at 45% after much thought and discussion.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The opening of the new sports block was the biggest ____ in the school's history.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its ____ updating, people will be able to discover new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During various stages of a planning process, review and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not ____ one another.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are definitely going to fail the ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will not have to ____ permission to publish if the purpose of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The rules of the school ____ that you must leave your mobile phone in your locker and not bring it to class.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The President will ____ on TV this evening to talk about the riots in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They must not be allowed to ____ the emergence of a competitive market economy.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Strong families possess the ability to ____ both daily stressors and difficult life crises creatively and effectively.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is virtually impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not ____ without support.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Ventures like Amazon.com will only continue to ____ as long as they make money.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He ____ failed to mention the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While this was a great idea, the ____ were unclear about the requirements and how it would be graded.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Certain questions must be answered before it becomes politically feasible, or even necessary, to ____ cellular phones.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ that at least 80% of the students will pass with the top grade.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I tried to ____ the information on the internet, but could find nothing useful.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has removed a ____ of the report which they said was no longer up-to-date.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This note describes a scoring ____ for the co-reference task in MUC6.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed ____ of the student and signed consent of the parent.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a ____ or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is thinking about introducing courses to ____ young people how to be good parents.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He claimed that the Pacific Tsunami Warning Centre knew about the tsunami ahead of time but failed to ____ affected countries.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Very few students are allowed to ____ the course, and permission is by petition only.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Stopping work to look after a new-born child must not be allowed to interfere with a woman's ____ chances.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some parents do not ____ their daughters to go on school trips.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete ____ the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do you think that the school will ____ the suggestion to increase the number of holidays?", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences ____ which might contribute to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students ____ careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to ____ him and inform him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The results represented an unusual ____ of old and modern practices.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its ____ or content.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "From the quality of the writing I can only ____ that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They must ____ their information so that it is easy for the observer to understand the historical significance of their event.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The University will ____ the cost of the premiums for graduate students during the coming academic year.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to manipulate an array of numbers, so that your computer ____ executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sometimes it becomes more important to ____ tried-and-tested methods and habits rather than allocate more resources.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the ____ that she projected and the need to preserve her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I find it quite hard to understand why anyone would attempt to refute or ____ these accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a unique search ____ has paid off.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The idea was to ____ the possibility of a local court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The self-hatred that this ____ inflicted led the children to attempt to wash their skin white with scouring powder.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a new computer for each of its teachers.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each section of the book, is represented by a family, which was chosen as an ____ family representing that country.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ and often unclear structure of the organizational responsibilities enabled energetic managers to network.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Assign students to groups; establish rules for participation, and ____ jobs within each group.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Parents and children often ____ in their opinions on the importance of keeping bedrooms clean and tidy.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is some ____ that she will turn in her work on time. She's not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government expects to ____ resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is looking for students who would like to do voluntary work at the ____ old people's home.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The radioactivity in the drugs works to ____ the tumor but usually does not damage healthy organs.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ and often unclear structure of the organizational responsibilities enabled energetic managers to network.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is ____ that the summer rate cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of the project will include all processes, people, organizational structures, systems and facilities currently in place.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He started searching for ____ of Wilson's existence and eventually succeeded in documenting her life up to 1863.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Until ____ there have been few sources of information about the morphological and syntactic structure of the Kam language.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the ____ was not steady with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most people were ____ the plan to boycott the Olympics. Nevertheless, the government decided to do so.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The private ____ offers many opportunities for students with a history or liberal arts background.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He's having a lot of problems learning English, ____ in grammar and spelling.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to ____ new understanding.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The soldier shot the dog for no ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The study included a ____ of the main concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government decided to ____ their plans after thousands of people demonstrated on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company's ____ is that they will increase exports by 20% next year.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Color did not ____ the perceived sweetness of the drink and did not ____ the drink's ability to quench thirst.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As the earthquake waves travel, they ____ all of the principles of other types of wave motion.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to make inferences and hold causal beliefs, even though it is not rational.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The American colonists did not ____ a real newspaper of their own for another century.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Biological processes ____ strongly with physical and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The University may ____ the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written notice to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Where can I ____ about the teaching job I saw in the newspaper?", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is NOT a ____ statistic and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They simply decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that ____ (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people think that the ____ way to stop people smoking is to raise the price of cigarettes sky-high.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Before the ban on smoking in public places there was usually a ____ cloud of smoke at the end of the evening in bars and restaurants.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "So far scientists have been unable to ____ in their efforts to find a cure for cancer.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to ____ and coordinate their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences ____ improve performance over time.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally ____ bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are unable to attend a class for any reason, and would prefer to work directly from the student guide, please ____ the Training Coordinator.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Factory farming is just not ____ with animal welfare.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company has ____ plans to increase its business by 50% in the next two years.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Gladwin County decided to ____ the sale of dogs from its animal shelter in order to give citizens the chance to review the county's earlier decision.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first ____ all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study ____ in the Netherlands, you may be eligible for a grant for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Learning to value and ____ the differences of the people around you is an important part of a liberal arts education.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He has made substantial ____ this trimester.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government intends to found a new organization to help young people find ____ jobs.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some farmers, ____ those producing corn, hope that biofuels have a bright future, both as a new source of cheap energy and as a new source of revenue.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to improve student scores in standardized tests by doing 5 minutes practice at the start of every lesson.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most governments refuse to ____ with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}]]